

Profile

Max yu 1990.9.5 +86 17769712562 China / Chinese citizen x315043655@outlook.com zhejiang construction tech school major:construction field engineering

Excellent communication skills with a colorful and Positive personality which was built by my Rich experience.

Tough and reliable, capable in many scenario, in detail you can find me never late for work, can handle things and get the job done, get my team covered, get in to work deep and hard.

Physically hard to get sick or Injured, Quick reaction, Quick recovery from damage, both eyesight are at 5.2~5.3.

WEBSITE:

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC8aj 3Xp8DbDLqCjYg3C3ERQ/videos?view=0& sort=dd&shelf_id=0

HOBBIES

Travel by motorcycles Adventure Photography Camping Video game

Max Yu

my portfolio https://dinnexbell.github.io/resume-beyond/

apply because I love the things I do

location :anywhere(will be wonderful if remote are possible) working hours : flexible for work

if I'm not fit for this specific opportunity ,I'm flexible and willing to take other position that May better fit my qualification

Native English(American accent) and Chinese.

Familiar with HTML CSS JavaScript react vue, Python for Django , automation with selenium.

Experience servers and vpn technology.

A fast learner with powerful logic thinking ,able to comprehend technical concept explain with non-technical language.

technical support/customer service experience, excellent communication skills, Empathy with customers, understand how customers feel.

Rich knowledge about Microsoft products, such as Windows10 and Windows server, one drive ,SharePoint ,Azure general Resources, great passion and ability to help, troubleshooting & break fix ,make things happen ,deploy professional software.

Great passion and ability to maintain a complex system in optimal condition , happen to see things running fast and fluid.

Experience as a technical support engineer working for Microsoft, supporting professional line for troubleshooting & break fix.

Familiarity with OS Internals concepts (Windows, Linux, etc.), Storage, Active Directory and Security.

Deep Understanding features on Windows, concepts and system administration.

Knowledge with Azure general resource and feature, configuration and administration.

Familiarity with networking tools/protocols (tcp/ip, http, ping, tracert, tracemon, wire shark, etc.)

About myself:

Strong will, Optimistic adventurer, honest and with integrity.

I used to cross Mountains and sea, walk past small villages and bustling bazaars, sitting in a warm night market ,Listening to the wind chimes float and the cooking smoke rising and spin, I camped in snowy mountains at high altitude, look for a place can cover the frozen wind, I soldier through steaming hot sun ,I see the ordinary life of everyone and how they live their life, and Learned how to find peace within me.







EXPERIENCE

Wicresoft/Microsoft, shanghai—support engineer

2018 - 2019

As part of an outsource support team, help customers with Microsoft products ,including ,system diagnosis,troubleshoot ,break fix software problems , general inquiry,customers support,I was a power and effective team player.

zhejiang shengheng international, overseas — salesman

2014 - 2017

As part of an overseas sales team ,providing clothes material in Arabian community , Make friends with locals , Monitor the market, explore and expand, and I was a resourceful and effective team player .

EDUCATION

zhejiang construction technology school,

hangzhou— Construction engineer

September 2009- September 2013

I study hard ,play hard ,do what i loved, supporting and working for an animal Shelter, Won a scholarship, time pass ,get a paper.